const localTalentMediumQuestions = [
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'Which of these is not a musical term?',
    answers: ['Sharp', 'Flat', 'Point'],
    correct: 'Point',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'Which string has the highest tone?',
    answers: ['A', 'G', 'B'],
    correct: 'B',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'Where is the bridge on a guitar?',
    answers: [
      'At the top of the neck',
      'On the body',
      'On the underside of the guitar',
    ],
    correct: 'On the body',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'What note sounds the most “bright”?',
    answers: ['Major', 'Minor', 'Grande'],
    correct: 'Major',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: 'Which “clef” is used for guitar?',
    answers: ['Treble', 'Bass', 'Hue'],
    correct: 'Treble',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'What is the third string from the top of a guitar?',
    answers: ['G', 'D', 'A'],
    correct: 'D',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'How many frets are held down for a “D” chord?',
    answers: ['3', '4', '5'],
    correct: '3',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'What is a rest?',
    answers: ['A nap', 'A pause in music theory', 'A drawn out note'],
    correct: 'A pause in music theory',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: 'What is a chord?',
    answers: [
      'A music symbol',
      'A type of note',
      'A series of notes played in unison',
    ],
    correct: 'A series of notes played in unison',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: 'Which note is held for longer?',
    answers: ['A whole note', 'A quarter note', 'A half note'],
    correct: 'A whole note',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: 'What is a riff?',
    answers: [
      'A repeated chord progression or refrain',
      'A type of chord',
      'A part of the guitar by the neck',
    ],
    correct: 'A repeated chord progression or refrain',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: 'Which is the sign for a sharp?',
    answers: ['m', '^', '#'],
    correct: '#',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question: 'A beat is...',
    answers: ['A unit of time', 'A dance move', 'How loud or soft to play'],
    correct: 'A unit of time',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 41,
    question: 'Which is a faster tempo?',
    answers: ['90bpm', '50bpm', '120bpm'],
    correct: '120bpm',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: 'How many frets are held down for an Em chord?',
    answers: ['2', '4', '1'],
    correct: '2',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: 'Which note comes after E?',
    answers: ['E#', 'F', 'Em'],
    correct: 'F',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: 'How many beats are in a bar with a 4/4 time signature?',
    answers: ['5', '8', '4'],
    correct: '4',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question: 'What is an octave?',
    answers: [
      'A type of instrument',
      'Two notes of different pitches that share a letter name',
      'A chord that is played slowly',
    ],
    correct: 'Two notes of different pitches that share a letter name',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 46,
    question: 'Which is a guitar technique?',
    answers: ['Hammer-offs', 'Hammer-ons', 'Hammersons'],
    correct: 'Hammer-ons',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question: 'Which is a guitar technique?',
    answers: ['Slides', 'Sliders', 'Slips'],
    correct: 'Slides',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: 'Which is a guitar technique?',
    answers: ['Bonds', 'Benders', 'Bends'],
    correct: 'Bends',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 65,
    question: 'What are the names of the lines on a staff?',
    answers: ['E G B D F', 'A D E F B', 'B A C D E'],
    correct: 'E G B D F',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 66,
    question: 'What is a pull off?',
    answers: [
      'A strumming technique that uses pulling',
      'Pulling to pluck a string with your fret fingers',
      'Neither',
    ],
    correct: 'Pulling to pluck a string with your fret fingers',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 67,
    question: 'How many frets are held down for an Am chord?',
    answers: ['3', '4', '6'],
    correct: '3',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 68,
    question: 'The five lines that notes are written on is called a...',
    answers: ['Bar', 'Line', 'Staff'],
    correct: 'Staff',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 69,
    question: 'What does an m after a note mean?',
    answers: ['Micro', 'Minor', 'Minismo'],
    correct: 'Minor',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 70,
    question: 'Which notes do not have sharps?',
    answers: ['B and E', 'E and G', 'E and F'],
    correct: 'B and E',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 71,
    question: 'What symbol signifies a “flat”?',
    answers: ['-', 'm', 'b'],
    correct: 'b',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 72,
    question:
      'What note would be played if you held down the first fret of the low E string?',
    answers: ['G', 'E#', 'F'],
    correct: 'F',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 73,
    question: 'What symbol indicates the sound or pitch?',
    answers: ['b', 'A note', '#'],
    correct: 'A note',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 74,
    question: 'How many lines are in a musical staff?',
    answers: ['6', '7', '5'],
    correct: '5',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    question: 'How many notes make a chord?',
    answers: ['No more than 4', '2 or more', 'No less than 3'],
    correct: '2 or more',
    answeredBefore: false,
    difficulty: 'medium',
    reward: 2,
  },
]

export { localTalentMediumQuestions }
